{
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "It is easy _________ her.",
      "a": "for us to get on with",
      "b": "that we get on with",
      "c": "our getting on with",
      "d": "get on with",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Be easy for sb to V",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is it necessary ___ the book immediately?",
      "a": "his returning",
      "b": "that he returns",
      "c": "for him to return",
      "d": "to him return",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Be necessary for sb to V",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is certain ___ the examination.",
      "a": "for her to pass",
      "b": "her passing",
      "c": "her to pass",
      "d": "that he will pass",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Be certain that + clause",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "She was very ___ when I told her my pet dog died.",
      "a": "sympathetic",
      "b": "helpful",
      "c": "pitiful",
      "d": "friendly",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Sympathetic (adj): Caring and feeling sorry about someone's problems",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Palm trees are native to ___ climates.",
      "a": "cold",
      "b": "warm",
      "c": "cool",
      "d": "wet",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Palm trees often live in tropical forests",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "We felt ___ when we realized that perhaps we had offended Mr. Lee.",
      "a": "uncomfortable",
      "b": "uncomfortably",
      "c": "comfortably",
      "d": "comfort",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- To feel + adjective",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Coffee mixed with chicory is likely to taste ___ to a person not used to it.",
      "a": "well",
      "b": "bitter",
      "c": "sweetly",
      "d": "bitterly",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- To taste + adjective",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Has your lost Ford been located? \"It was found ___on the highway.\"",
      "a": "to be abandoned",
      "b": "to be abandoning",
      "c": "abandoned",
      "d": "abandon",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- To find + obj + past participle.Â \n- To be found + past participle.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are you going to the concert with me? \"That's a good idea, but I'm afraid it ___ expensive\"",
      "a": "much too",
      "b": "too much",
      "c": "very greatly",
      "d": "seems",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Seem + adjective",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you think the news is true? \"Yes, ___\"",
      "a": "I am sure of its being true",
      "b": "I am sure of being true",
      "c": "I am not sure it to be true",
      "d": "I am sure it not to be true",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "I am sure of its being true = I am sure (that) it is true.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "5"
    }
  ]
}